Anne Morrow Lindbergh Papers, 1892-1993
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. WRITINGS
  - North to the Orient
    - Corrected typescripts, pt. 2Feb - Apr 1934 (Box 74, Folder 1-3)
    - Corrected typescripts, undated (Box 74, Folder 4-9)
    - Galley proofs (Box 75, Folder 1-4)
    - English hardcover editions, 1935 (Box 76, Folder 1-2)
    - Condensed version, 1935 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Reader's Digest version, 1937 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous bulletins, correspondence, and financial items collected during the Lindbergh's trip and concerning the publication of AML's book (Box 76, Folder 5-6)
    - Original photographs of the Lindberghs with native people in Alaska and a meeting of the Lindberghs with a Japanese official (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Clippings and articles concerning the book's publication, 1935-37 (Box 77, Folder 2-7)
    - Maps, used by CAL and AML during their flight to Alaska and Asia (Box 78, Folder 1-22)
    - "Hubbard Medal Award" material; AMLs' report on flooding in China (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Museum objects, including CAL's wallet; passports; cloth sack; and labels (Box 79, Folder 2-5)
    - Smith College miscellany, including materials concerning the planning of an exhibit of AML's manuscripts and museum objects for a 2001 exhibition (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Listen! The Wind
    - English hardcover editions, 1938 (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
    - English paperback edition, 1938 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Dutch paperback translation (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - German paperback translation editions (Box 81, Folder 1-2)
    - Newspaper articles and clippings
      - 1938 - Feb 1939 (Box 81, Folder 3-12)
      - Mar 1939 - Jan 1940 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - "An Analysis of Two Travel Diaries with Malice toward Some and Listen, [sic] The Wind" by William H. F. Lamont, Rutgers University (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - "O to Whom"
    - Handwritten and typed manuscripts (Box 82, Folder 3-6)
    - Typed carbons of poems (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Typed carbons of poems (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Second typed carbons of poems (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Discarded poems (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous writings (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Wave of the Future, English hardcover edition (1940) (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - The Steep Ascent
    - English hardcover edition (1944) (Box 83, Folder 6-7)
    - English paperback reprint (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Gift from the Sea
    - "The Shells" MS
      - Handwritten MS, early drafts and outlines, undated (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - "Beach Thoughts," first drafts, undated (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Draft sent to Lucia Valentine and Alan Valentine, May 1951 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - "The Argonauta," Draft for CAL, 28 May 1951 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Early drafts,including CAL draft (with letter) 1951 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Incomplete typed copy (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Incomplete typed copy, last copies of "Double Sunrise" and "Argonauta," August 1951 (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - "The Shells" MS, notes and excerpts from other authors (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Harper's Bazaar copy (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Handwritten notes and drafts (Box 84, Folder 10-11)
    - Early carbon copy of MS, returned by Barbara Stuart (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Typed MS, complete 1953 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Typed MSS, Aug 1953 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - "Three Shells," published version, Jan 1955 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Publisher's MS, Jan 1954 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Corrected MS pages, Jan - Feb 1954 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Notes and drafts, Jan - Apr 1954 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - "Old Copy - Jan 1954, recopied Apr 1954" 1954 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Publishers carbon copy of MS, Feb - Apr 1954 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - CAL copies (with letters) (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Typed MS, "Preface" (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Galley proofs and AML's notes (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Last corrected galley (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Reviews and clippings (Box 86, Folder 3-5)
    - English hardcover editions (Box 86, Folder 6-7)
    - English hardcover editions (Box 87, Folder 1-2)
    - Fan letters and correspondence
      - Dec 1954 - Mar 1955 (Box 87, Folder 3-6)
      - Mar - Apr 1955 (Box 88, Folder 1-7)
      - Apr 1955 (Box 89, Folder 1-6)
      - May 1955 (Box 90, Folder 1-7)
      - May - Jun 1955 (Box 91, Folder 1-6)
      - Jul - Aug 1955 (Box 92, Folder 1-7)
      - Sep - Oct 1955 (Box 93, Folder 1-7)
      - Oct - Nov 1955 (Box 94, Folder 1-7)
      - Nov - Jan 1956 (Box 95, Folder 1-6)
      - Jan - Apr 1956 (Box 96, Folder 1-8)
      - Apr - Jul 1956 (Box 97, Folder 1-6)
      - Jul - Nov 1956 (Box 98, Folder 1-7)
      - Dec 1956 - Mar 1957 (Box 99, Folder 1-7)
      - Apr - Dec 1957 (Box 100, Folder 1-10)
      - Jan - Dec 1958, undated (Box 101, Folder 1-3)
    - English paperback edition (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Foreign language editions: Arabic, Bengali, Burmese, Chinese, and Danish (Box 101, Folder 5-9)
    - Dutch, German, Italian, Japanese, Marathi, Portuguese, and Swedish (Box 102, Folder 1-7)
    - Shortened English language hardcover ed., 1967 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - The Unicorn
    - Notes and drafts (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Printer's MSS, from Pantheon (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Corrected typescripts (Box 102, Folder 3-5)
    - Galley proofs and binding jacket (Box 102, Folder 6-8)
    - English hardcover editions, 1956 (Box 102, Folder 9-10)
    - Fan letters and other correspondence, 1952-1957 (Box 104, Folder 1-8)
    - Reviews and advertisements (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Articles about, including discussion of John Ciardi's review (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Dearly Beloved
    - Handwritten and early drafts, 1958-59 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Notes and miscellany, 1959-1961 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Handwritten chapters, undated (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Chpt. I, notes and drafts, 1958-59 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Chpt. I, notes and drafts, undated (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Chpt. II, notes and drafts, Fall 1958 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Chpt. II-III, notes and drafts, undated (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - "Andre" and "Chrissie" chapters, 1956-61 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - "Andre" chapter, revisions and drafts, 1957 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, notes, and drafts, 1957 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - "The Supper" chapter, notes and drafts, 1957-59 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - "Deborah" chapter, notes and drafts, 1958-59 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - "Aunt Harriet" chapter, notes and drafts, 1959 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - "Aunt Harriet" chapter, notes and drafts, undated (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Chpt. III, notes and drafts, Jun 1959 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - "Beatrice" chapter, notes and drafts, 1960-61 (Box 107, Folder 4-6)
    - Typed carbon copy, corrected, 1959-61 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Corrected typescript of MS, Jun 1960 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - "The Bride and Groom" chapter, notes and drafts, Sep 1960 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Addenda, Jun 1961 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - "After" chapter, notes and drafts, Jun - Oct 1961 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - "Don" chapter, drafts and revisions, 1958-60 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - "Pierre" chapter, notes and drafts, 1959-61 (Box 108, Folder 1-3)
    - "Theodore" chapter, notes and drafts, 1959-60 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - "Frances" chapter, notes, drafts, and correspondence, 1955-61 (Box 108, Folder 5-10)
    - "The Toast" chapter, notes and drafts, 1959-61 (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
    - Corrected typescript, carbon copy, 1959 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Corrected typed carbons, Mar 1961 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Notes on MS, Apr 1961 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Typed carbon copies, with notes, May - Dec 1961 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Corrected typescript, Mar - Nov 1961 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Edited typescript, 3 Dec 1961 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - AMLs and CAL's notes on corrections and suggestions of others, Dec. 1961 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Corrected galley proofs (Box 110, Folder 2-3)
    - Correspondence and biographical materials (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - "A Safari Back to Innocence"
    - Research materials (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Notes and drafts (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Life copy, 21 Oct 1966 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - "An African Essay," Filmstrip script, Jan - Mar 1969 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - "The Heron and the Astronaut"
    - Research materials, 1968-69 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Research materials, 1968-69 (Box 111, Folder 1-3)
    - First typed draft, Feb 1969 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Last typed draft, Feb 1969 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Corrected galleys, with correspondence, Feb 1969 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Signed Life magazine copy, 28 Feb 1969 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Earth Shine
    - Notes and drafts (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Last MS and page proofs, May 1969 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Preface: Notes and drafts (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Hardcover copy,signed by AML and CAL 1969 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - "Earth Values"
    - Research materials, 1968-70 (Box 113, Folder 1-5)
    - Notes and drafts (Box 113, Folder 6-7)
    - Notes and drafts (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Final typed draft (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Copy read at meeting, Feb 1970 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Sound recording, Smith College commencement address, Feb 1970 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Published versions in Explorer, Smith Alumnae Quarterly, and Chapin Alumnae Bulletin, 1970-71 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Nov 1969 - Apr 1970 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Bring Me a Unicorn
    - First typed MS, edited (from 4 original envelopes) (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - First yyped MS, edited (Box 115, Folder 1-3)
    - Typed MS, "Later insertions in Vol. 1" (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - First typed MS, "Pages deleted before typescript was copied" (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Notes by AML on reading MS (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, typed carbons (letters considered for publication) (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Published hardcover edition, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Review (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Hour of Gold, Hour of Lead
    - First typed MS, edited (from 4 original envelopes) (Box 116, Folder 1-4)
    - First typed MS/Letters rejected from MS (Box 116)
      - AML to CAL, 1928-29 (Box 116, Folder 5)
      - AML to ECM, 1929-32 (Box 116, Folder 6)
      - AML to ELLL, ECM to ELLL, 1928-31 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - AML to ELLL, ECM to ELLL (Box 116, Folder 8)
      - AML to aunts and grandmother, 1907-33 (Box 116, Folder 9)
      - AML to sisters, 1929-32 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Notes on proposed MS (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Introduction, handwritten notes and drafts, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 2-4)
    - "Last Notes," Apr - Jun 1972 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1970-73 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Published hardcover edition, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Locked Rooms and Open Doors
    - Discarded letters (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Misc. letters, containing typed carbon copies of letters to AML's family 1933-35 (Box 118, Folder 2-5)
    - Introduction drafts, Mar - Apr 1973 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Xeroxed pages for AML, Apr 1973 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Corrected typescript, with AML's corrections in blue pencil (Box 118, Folder 8-9)
    - First copy edited by AML (pp. 1-102) (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - First copy edited by AML (pp. 103-930) (Box 119, Folder 1-5)
    - First carbon of first typed draft, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - First carbon of first typed draft, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Revised MS of 1933 letters, and intro., Jul 1973 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Last typescript before galleys, Aug 1973 (Box 120, Folder 3-4)
    - Misc. notes and correspondence (Box 120, Folder 5-6)
    - Published hardcover edition, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - The Flower and the Nettle
    - Letters and diary entries considered for publication, including rejects and discards (Box 121, Folder 2-9)
    - Letters and diary entries considered for publication, including rejects and discards (Box 122, Folder 1-6)
    - Corrected original typescript (pp. 1-258) (Box 122, Folder 7-8)
    - Corrected original typescript (pp. 259-780) (Box 123, Folder 1-3)
    - Corrected Xerox copy of typescript (pp. 1-278) (Box 123, Folder 4-5)
    - Corrected Xerox copy of typescript (pp. 279a-810) (Box 124, Folder 1-3)
    - Corrected Xeorx copy (pp. 1-443) (Box 124, Folder 4-6)
    - Corrected typescript (pp. 444-810) (Box 125, Folder 1-3)
    - Typescript carbon copies, with all cuts and corrections (pp. 1-913) (Box 125, Folder 4-6)
    - Corrected typed carbons (pp. 914-1604) (Box 126, Folder 1-3)
    - Notes, drafts, and correspondence concerning the writing of the introduction, including a note by Reeve Lindbergh (Box 126, Folder 4-8)
    - Notes taken on first and second readings (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Misc. notes and correspondence (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Corrected galleys (Box 127, Folder 3-4)
    - Notes taken on galleys and books read (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - War Within and Without
    - Carbon and Xerox copies of correspondence, poems, and diary entries considered for publication 1940-47 (Box 128, Folder 1-6)
    - Carbon copies of correspondence, poems, and diary entries considered for publication 1940-47 (Box 129, Folder 1-6)
    - Carbon copies of correspondence, poems, and diary entries considered for publication 1940-47 (Box 130, Folder 1-5)
    - Corrected typescript (pp. 1-202) (Box 130, Folder 6-7)
    - Corrected typescript (pp. 203-875) (Box 131, Folder 1-5)
    - Corrected carbon copies of typescript (pp. 1-197) (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Corrected carbon copies of typescript (pp. 198-1348) (Box 132, Folder 1-2)
    - Corrected carbon copies (pp. 1-875) (Box 132, Folder 3-6)
    - Corrected carbon copies (pp. 501-2040) (Box 133, Folder 1-7)
    - Corrected typescript (Xerox copies) (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Dates and inserts (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Condensation work on special pages, Feb. 1978 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Notes on books read by AML in preparation for writing introduction (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Introduction: notes and drafts (Box 134, Folder 3-8)
    - AML's notes on reading MS, Jul 1973 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Corrected galley proofs (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence concerning publication, including letters to AML's publisher Helen Wolff (Box 135, Folder 2-4)
  - Miscellaneous unpublished writings
    - Childhood writings, 1915-20 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous poetry, carbon copies (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - "Yellow Notebook," ca. 1928-40 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Comments on flooding in China, Aug 1931, typed carbon copy (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Notes on Harold Nicholson's biography of Dwight W. Morrow, 1935 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Untitled World War II era writings (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - "Marking Time," Review of While We Are Absent,revised typed copy 1943 (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - "Edward Sheldon," written after Sheldon's death in 1946 ca. 1946 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - "Moments of Joy," etc., typed carbon copies 1947 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - "Airliner to Europe," Notes and drafts, 1947 (Box 136, Folder 3-5)
    - "For Better or for Worse," concerning AML's wedding vows ca. 1949 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Notes and comments on Betsey Barton book, As Love is Deep 1956 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - "Thurs December 8th 1959," Typed carbon copy (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - "Mrs. Johnson-White House Image," corrected typed carbon copy ca. 1963-64 (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - "Musical Chairs," 1981 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - "The Breughal," undated (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Poems, rejected by AML taken out of folder "Early Ones and Poor Ones" (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous poems and writings, undated (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous published writings
    - "Flood and Famine in China, " 1932 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - "Flying Around the North Atlantic," National Geographic, signed, 1934 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - "Hubbard Medal awarded to AML," National Geographic, 1934 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - "Wartime Waiting," The Progressive, 12 Jul 1943 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - "The Flame of Europe," Jan 1948 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - "One Starts at Zero," Reader's Digest, Feb 1948 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - "Anywhere in Europe," Harper's Magazine, Apr 1948 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - "Airliner to Europe," Harper's, Sep 1948 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - "The Mother and the Child," from Harper's, Dec 1948 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - "Our Lady of Risk," Life, Jul 1950 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Anthology of Magazine Verse for 1958, containing poems by AML (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - The Diaries and Letters of Anne Morrow Lindbergh, 1922-1944, A Sampler 1993 (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous poems (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Writings Kept by AML
    - "Autobiography of an Ex-Feminist," 1933 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - World War II miscellany, 1943-44 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - "The Jon Lindbergh Story" (from This Week magazine) Feb 1953 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Copy of Saturday Review, Aug 1953 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - The Man Who Lived Twice by Eric W. Barnes, 1956 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - "The Annual Crisis of Love," from Life magazine, Dec 1965 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous writings kept by AML, 1970s-1980s (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Excerpts from other authors, undated (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Manuscript by Arthur Train, Jr., on Alexis Carrel, undated (Box 138, Folder 9)
- SERIES V. CHARLES A. LINDBERGH
  - Diaries
    - Typed carbon copies, 1912-33 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Typed carbon copies, 20 Nov 1937 - 5 Aug 1938 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Original and typed carbon copies, 6 Aug - 17 Oct 1938 (Box 139, Folder 3-6)
    - Original and typed carbon copies, 17 Oct 1938 - 3 Nov 1938 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Typed carbon copies, 4 Nov 1938 - 14 Aug 1940 (Box 140, Folder 2-8)
    - Typed carbon copies, 14 Aug 1940 - 17 Apr 1944 (Box 141, Folder 1-6)
    - Typed carbon copies, 18 Apr 1944 - 25 Jun 1945 (Box 142, Folder 1-4)
  - Correspondence
    - CAL to Evangeline Lodge Land Lindbergh, typed carbon copies, 1915-25 (Box 142, Folder 5-9)
    - Typed carbon copies, CAL to ELLL, 1926-46, undated (Box 143, Folder 1-5)
    - Misc. correspondence and other papers, 1929-40 (Box 143, Folder 6-12)
    - Misc. correspondence and other papers, 1944-69, undated (Box 144, Folder 1-2)
  - Writings by CAL
    - Flight Logs,typed carbon copies (originals at Missouri Historical Society) 1922-44 (Box 144, Folder 3-7)
    - Airforce reports, 1942 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Military documents, 1941-61 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous writings,typed carbons, with slight corrections 1928-36 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - "To Bogota and Back by Air," National Geographic, 1928 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - "Collecting Micro-Organisms from the Arctic Atmosphere," 1935 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Notebook, containing autobiographical information, typed carbon copyDec 1938 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - "33 Hours to Paris," The Saturday Evening Post, 1953 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - "The Wisdom of Wildness," Life, 1967 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - "A Letter from Lindbergh," Life, Aug 1969 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous addresses and speeches, 1939-54 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Writings about CAL
    - "The Dance in Lindbergh's Honor," 1927 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - "Who Ride (song)," 1927 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - "Lindbergh in Paris," 1927 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - "Seeing America with Lindbergh," National Geographic, 1928 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - "President Coolidge bestows Lindbergh Award," 1928 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 1927-71 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbooks
    - Kept by Willard S. Morse, purchased by ECM from Dawson Book Shop in Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 145, Folder 13-15)
    - Illustrations of CAL from scrapbooks, undated (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - 1892 - Oct 1927 (Box 146, Folder 2-8)
    - Nov 1927 - Dec 1929 (Box 147, Folder 1-7)
    - 1930 - Mar 1932 (Box 148, Folder 1-6)
    - Mar 1932 - 1934 (Box 149, Folder 1-8)
  - New York Times scrapbooks
    - May - Dec 1927 (Box 150, Folder 1-10)
    - Jan 1928 - Feb 1932 (Box 151, Folder 1-10)
  - Books
    - Lindbergh the Lone Eagle by George B. Fife (1927) (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - The Spirit of St. Louis: One Hundred Poems, ed. by Charles Vale (1927) (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Charles Lindbergh: His Life by Dale Van Every and Morris D. Tracy (1927) (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - The Story of Lindbergh the Lone Eagle by Richard J. Beamish (1928) (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - The Boy's Story of Lindbergh The Lone Eagle by Richard J. Beamish (1928) (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Pioneers All! Achievements in Adventure by Joseph L. French (1929) (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Lindbergh: His Story in Pictures by Francis T. Miller (1929) (Box 154, Folder 1-2)
    - Aces of the Air, ed. by Joseph L. French (1930) (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - The Seven Skies by Harry F. Guggenheim (1930) (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - The Lindberghs by Lynn and Dora Haines (1931) (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - The Lindberghs: The Story of a Distinguished Family by P. J. O'Brien (1935) (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Ride on the Wind by Alice Dalgliesh (1956) (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Photographs (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Medal commemorating CAL's trip across the Atlantic (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Box, featuring The Spirit of St. Louis on the cover (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Map showing CAL's route across the Atlantic 1928 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Notebook, belonging to ELLL, typed carbon copy (49 pages) (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Oversize photographs of AML, CAL, and Lindbergh family members (Box 157, Folder 1-2)
- SERIES VI. ADDITIONAL MATERIALS
  - Part of Series I. Biographical
    - General
      - School Papers 1917-28 (Box 158, Folder 1-2)
  - Part of Series III. Correspondence
    - Generation III.
      - Constance Morrow Morgan 1928-42 (Box 158, Folder 3-11)
      - Constance Morrow Morgan 1928-42 (continued) (Box 159-160)
      - Constance Morrow Morgan 1956-59, undated (Box 161)
    - Generation II.
      - ECM illness and death 1954-55 (Box 162, Folder 1-6)